{
    "id": "943a47218d9c4885ba30bca232a3eb29",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t think I …………………. be able to come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87ee8692fd304a09b76292fcae3f0807"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… not come unless he is invited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c2b35138e509418db7a8a63e0304ff2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… be punctual.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ought",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "652ea56b3260448a93308cb4fa487dfe"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I help you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1644c47e75584062b0ee16893b66310f"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you mind moving a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "671efd6ab3c247fea6e52b6c70d436f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that I ……………… visit his home whenever I wanted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02622a62e79d49339e53c2d7f2548bac"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………. see her, give her my love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "29c315a41439413badc2ed9192554a68"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. you like another cup of coffee?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Could",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6362429a8a3f4a2fa8d324822157908e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ……………… not drive so fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e83de580fbd74037ac692ba81de9ba8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ………………… stop lying",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "00850cb201dc471c8df66c4b98a033c5"
        }
    ]
}